### **Ibrahim Omar Ibrahim**

Giza-Egypt 01018024013

<u>ibrahiim.omarr@gmail.com</u> <u>https://www.behance.net/hemaomar</u>

### **SUMMARY**

Creative and innovative Motion Graphic Designer with over 4 years of experience in the field. Specializing in 2D animation and cut-out animation techniques, I bring a unique blend of artistic vision and technical expertise to every project I undertake.

## **Work Experience**

Freelance (2023-current)

2D Animator AND Motion graphic designer (freelance)

I worked on preparing and animating motion graphics videos (used illustrator and After effect)

Learn n' Digital (2021-current)

2D Animator (Full Time)

I worked on animating children's stories (used **Moho** and **After effect**)

Chefaa (2020-2021)

Motion graphic designer (Full Time)

I worked on preparing and animating motion graphics videos (used illustrator and After effect)

Master Key Company (2019-2020)

**Video Editing (Full Time)** 

I worked on filming and editing e-learning videos (used premiere pro and After effect)

#### **EDUCATION**

Animation And Rigging In moho From Motion TripArt of Motion from Yanfaa

Motion Graphic from Motion Camp and motion design school

**3DS MAX And Vray from Russian Cultural Center** 

# **SKILLS**

Interpersonal skills:
Creativity
Listening and Accepting people's opinions
Fast learner and self-study person
TEAMWORK
Communication skills, presentation skills
skills:
Adobe software
3DS MAX
Maya
Rigging And Animation In Moho
Language skills:
English (Good)
VOLUNTEERING AND ACTIVITIES
Head of Video Editing at Our Vision CU (Nov2020 ) Head of Advertising workshop at Our Vision CU (Sep2019-May2020)